Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5900
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Southern Pacific Railroad and American Air Lines (Box 10)
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Airlines' Reply Brief, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Airlines' Exhibits 1-9, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Employees' Exhibit Mo. 1-3, 9-25, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - American Airlines Grievance No. P-03-88 Agreement, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    March 1, 1987
- Eastern Air Lines, MountainSide Transportation, Railroads, UPS, and Washington Gas Light (Box 11)
  - Eastern Air Lines Grievance No. 77-87, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Air Lines Grievance No. 91-87, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Air Lines Grievance No. 269-85, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Air Lines Grievance No. 282-87, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Air Lines Grievance No. 104-87, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Air Lines Grievance No. 1320-87, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Air Lines System Board of Adjustment, 1973-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Air Lines Awards and Decision, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railway Expedited Public Law Board No. 4595 Case No. 3, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Mountainside Transport Case No. 14-300-1477-890, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    January 23, 1990
  - Union Pacific Railroad ICC Finance Docket No. 30,000 Carrier's Submission, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Union Pacific Railroad ICC Finance Docket No. 30,000 Carrier's Exhibits No. A-E, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Union Pacific Railroad ICC Finance Docket No. 30,000 Carrier's Exhibits No. F-X, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Union Pacific Railroad ICC Finance Docket No. 30,000 Carrier's Exhibits No. Y-Z, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - United Parcel Service Case No. 90-31, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Washington Gas Light Company NYLIN Grievance, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Publications Government, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Publications Scholarly, 1963-1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jacob Seidenberg's High School Yearbook, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 19)